Yeah, frustrating. You know, it's um I
really start search with our offense
getting shut out. That's it's not who we
are. That's unacceptable. Um never saw
that coming. You know, I think we had
five trips, you know, to their side of
the field and came by with no points.
And um just again, that's as a play
caller that that starts with me. When
you walk away with no points, that's
there's a huge amount of accountability
that I got to take for that. Um but it
was just a overall very frustrating day.
I think we did some things that were
very unorthodox on offense um for us,
you know, just penalties, silly
penalties that were controllable on our
end. Um you know, and some possessions
where we had opportunities at points and
didn't walk away with anything. That was
that was frustrating.
>> What are your thoughts on the team's
effort?
>> Well, I thought defensively I I saw some
really good things. I mean, they they
pressured him. Um he didn't have a lot
of time in the pocket with three or four
sacks, got a turnover, had an
opportunity, had another one. I know. Um
they got us on a zero beater, you know,
where was something we practiced. We
were ready for it and they still got us
for a touchdown. So there there was some
um held three points in the second half.
You know, this is if my memory serves
correctly. So there was some some
effort, you know, that's I I didn't see
a lack of effort. I just saw a lack of
attention to detail maybe on offense
that really showed up. That was that was
disappointing.
>> What do you think were the reason for so
many drops today and how big were those
drops?
>> Yeah. Um, but it was everything, you
know, it wasn't just drops. It was it
was I think everybody involved in the
offense um has got to got to own up to
that performance today.
>> Zack Joe had a kind of a unique down
demeter on Wednesday. Did you notice
anything different from him this week?
>> No.
>> You had a lot of conviction after
Pittsburgh that you guys were going to
be in this until the very end.
>> Yeah. Is it stunning the fact that
you're sitting here with three weeks to
go [snorts] and
>> Yeah, it's Yeah, I think it's it's
frustrating to to score zero points, get
shut out at home. That's that's
unacceptable. Um, never in a million
years would I've seen that coming, you
know, but that's that's what happened
today. So, now we got to look at why
that happened and we got to be
accountable for it and and keep moving
forward.
>> Zack, why do you think you and your
group of coaches, administration, top to
bottom are the right group to lead you?
Yeah, I I believe in every I believe in
everybody we got.
>> You're [snorts] down 17 nothing. I
believe that drive that ended in the
pick six took like eight minutes.
>> Anything you guys could have done there
to try to speed that up?
>> Um we had some personnel issues
certainly with some injuries that we
were trying to balance there. Uh moments
we went tempo, moments we decided huddle
and try to make sure we got points on
the board.
>> So you all have been eliminated from
[snorts] playoff contention since 2020.
How tough is that for?
>> Yeah, it's frustrating. This is a team
that I thought was a talented team that
was going to have a chance to do big
things this year.
>> What was [snorts] your message in the
locker room just now?
>> Uh, very similar.
>> Was Joe Was Joe Sharp in practice
throughout the week?
>> Yes.
>> How do you feel like he played today?
>> Um, I'll let him speak to that, but I I
know that there's some plays that he's
going to want to come back.
>> Two weeks ago, you know, you guys were
able to do anything at will really
against Baltimore on Thanksgiving.
Today, did anything surprise you that
they brought?
>> I wouldn't say that. I I would say, you
know, it it maybe looked easier than it
really was. you know, our defense, it
was five turnovers, five to nothing. Um,
early on, we kicked field goals in that
game when when you'd like to come away
with touchdowns. They made it really
hard. So, we knew that that wasn't
people were going to say that, you know,
that we won how we won and that was easy
for us. It wasn't. It was far from easy.
You know, we scored on two third downs
in that game. Um, touchdowns. So, we
knew that this game was going to be very
difficult and we put a lot of time and
effort into the plan and the practice.
And, um, I got to today feeling feeling
really good about where we're at. And
again, we just I'm not going to say that
there was a single area, particularly on
offense, that we're going to say that
was that was nearly good enough. It
wasn't even close to good enough
anywhere starting with me. And so that
that part was frustrating.
>> Why is complimentary football been
difficult for this team to find this
season?
>> Yeah, that's that's the hard one for me
to answer. Hasn't been good enough.
>> What's what's the where y'all go from
here three games out? What's the main
objection?
>> Find a way to win. Just just approach
every single week as if we're still in
it. still got something to play for and
that's our responsibility and that's
what we're going to continue to do.
>> Aside from just overall wins, what would
you like to see the most as you guys
finished out the season?
>> Wins would be the number one thing.
>> What did you see from guys this week?
Obviously, you got split playoff hopes
coming in. It was a big game at home
against Baltimore.
>> Yeah, it was important to everybody. I I
didn't see anything. Um, and again, this
is if you told me our defense was going
to sack him as many times and and harass
him in the pocket and create a turnover
and holding three points in the second
half, I'd sign up for that, you know.
So, again, just just wholesale as a
team, we weren't good enough today.
>> Fans are going to [clears throat] want
to uh obviously see some changes over
the next three weeks or so, giving them
hope for 2026. What is your message to
the fans?
>> Just hang with us. It's been
frustrating. Um, we're still pouring our
heart and soul into this thing and find
a way to win and it's it's been a
frustrating season. I understand that.
>> Just to follow up on that, I know you're
just looking at this game, but looking
big picture, three years of of not
making the playoffs, what would you like
to say to the fans that will give them a
vote of confidence that you guys can get
[snorts] this right and they won't be
feeling like this next?
>> Yeah, I've got great confidence. I mean,
we we come to work every single day. I
believe in the guys we got in this
locker room, coaches and players and and
um frustrating frustrating season so
far. We still got a couple games left.
>> Zack, why was Joe in there on that last
possession?
>> Tough that. We just ended in a pick six.
Didn't give Flacko any time to warm up
and zero degree temperature basically.
So tried to manage it. Just hand the
ball off through a quick game. Things
that would keep them out of harm way. Um
obviously tough spot to be in. I'd say
if it was anything other than zero
degrees, we we probably would have
quickly made the change and and forego
the warmup. But um again just tried to
as we called it kept him out of harm's
way with just any throw we made the
ball's coming out quick.
>> Now that you are officially eliminated,
how do you keep players heads in it for
the last three weeks to to keep going
every day?
>> They're professionals, you know, and
that's that's why you build the locker
room the way you do it so that you don't
have to worry about guys like that. You
know, guys that they they know how
important this is not only for
themselves and their career, but for all
the work this team has put in. And
through good times and bad, go out there
and put your best foot forward. And I
absolutely trust that these guys will do
that.
Okay, thank you.